A Guide to the Ford Foundation records, International Division, Office Files of Elinor Barber FA632
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Subject Files, 1967-1981; II; 2.66 Cubic Feet 7 letter document boxes
  - Education, B
    - Sex Differences in Education - Meeting, Feb. 5, 1979, 1978-1979 (Box 13, Folder 191)
    - Rural Education, 1979-1980 (Box 13, Folder 192)
    - Rural Education (IIEP Seminar), 1975-1979 (Box 13, Folder 193)
    - HER Office Activities, 1975-1979 (Box 13, Folder 194)
    - HER Office Activities, 1970-1974 (Box 13, Folder 195)
    - March 1981 Information Paper - Education, 1980-1981 (Box 13, Folder 196)